pckeeper.com 2017-03-12

# PCKeeper Official Website

[Last Updated: 21/06/2016]

## Introduction

We, Essentware S.A. (hereinafter "Essentware"), are aware about privacy issues that occur during the usage of products, services and websites. Therefore we strictly follow all the data protection procedures aimed to preserve the complete security of your personal information. Our privacy policy applies to: 

  * using the Essentware’s products and services (hereinafter referred to as the “PCKeeper”),
  * visiting the [http://pckeeper.com](https://pckeeper.com/) website,
  * visiting any other linked pages or application services offered by the Essentware.

By doing all and any of the above you confirm that you accept our Privacy Policy.

The following Privacy Policy covers handling of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected by the Essentware when you use our products and services.

## 1\. Personal Information We Collect

We gather the following data from our customers:

### Information Provided by You

You will be required to provide the following personal information at our website or in any other way:

  * login and password,
  * your name,
  * contact details,
  * payment details, etc.

You can create a PCKeeper™ account using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you with an option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

Information provided by you will be used only for: 

  * creating an account that you will be able to manage Essentware PCKeeper licenses with, 
  * customer support CRM system, 
  * emails informing about news, updates, etc.

### Note

Information collected by some PCKeeper services you activated deliberately is not used by the Essentware for any purpose. This information can be accessed only by the user in the account page ( [PCKeeper account](https://account.pckeeper.com/)).   
This data enables fast and efficient rendering of PCKeeper services to our customers. In addition, it is used for communication purposes, such as notifying you about PCKeeper updates or special offers.  
The user is able to hide their personal data when creating a PCKeeper account as well as to deactivate PCKeeper services previously activated in their PCKeeper account.  
User information is not complemented by information from other sources. 

### Information Collected Automatically

In addition to information you enter yourself, we collect technical data such as:

  * IP addresses,
  * cookies,
  * browser Information, etc.

During registration of a PCKeeper account we will also collect such information, as customer’s name, email and phone number.

This data is used for the following purposes:

  * finding out how many people visit our website and how frequently,
  * learning how many people use our products and services,
  * finding out which products and services are used more frequently than others,
  * collecting some other statistical information.

### Information collected by PCKeeper: 

  * email address; 
  * IP address; 
  * information about your PC system (e.g. OS version, overall system information etc.); 
  * information about your apps (e.g. versions, size, date of the last update, etc.); 
  * results of Find & Fix scan.

Collected information is used for:

  * registration of the PCKeeper account;
  * proper functioning of the PCKeeper;
  * supplying you with a list of recommended fixes/software updates.

We may use collected information for online preference marketing. During the installation of PCKeeper you will have the opportunity to deny usage of your information for this purpose by unchecking the box related to this statement. You may also contact our Customer Support and cease usage of such information if you do not wish to receive ads based on your preferences. 

Should you want to delete your PCKeeper account, please contact our Customer Support.

Should you choose to activate some of the PCKeeper services, we will automatically collect the computer's IP address and its geographical position every hour to track location, trace route and make snapshots using the built-in camera or any external camera every five minutes.

Automatically gathered data is completely anonymous. Therefore, even if it is revealed to some third parties, this won’t affect your privacy.

## 2\. Information Collected via Email

Occasionally, you will receive customer satisfaction surveys via email where you will be asked to provide us with your opinion and some additional personal information. It will be used solely by us for our internal usage to improve our products and services, making your overall user experience better.

## 3\. Information Provided by Third Parties

We can use your personal information, such as email address, provided by third parties ( [e.g. Cleverbridge](http://www.cleverbridge.com/corporate/)) for our promotional activities such as notifying you about PCKeeper updates and special offers according to [Cleverbridge Privacy Policy](http://www.cleverbridge.com/corporate/privacy-policy/). If you don’t agree with this, please don’t proceed with the purchase of our PCKeeper.

## 4\. Cookies

We use cookies to track your actions on our website. These small text files are stored on your hard drive; they make it possible for our systems to recognize your browser. You can turn off cookies in your browser, but then you won’t have access to some of the essential features of our website.

## 5\. Email Communication

Occasionally, you will receive newsletters and various promotional materials from Essentware notifying you about PCKeeper updates or special offers. If you don’t want to receive such emails from us, you are free to unsubscribe from the mailing list.

## 6\. Sharing Your Personal Information

We respect and protect your private information, and do not disclose it to anyone. We will share your Personal Information only in the following cases:

  1. _with affiliates:_ in some cases we may closely cooperate with some companies and/or businesses, and your Personal Information may be required for various transactions with these partners.

  2. _with agents:_ we may employ other companies to act as intermediate parties for us; therefore we may share our customers’ private information with them. These agents won’t use your information for purposes other than assisting us.

  3. _for business transfers:_ customer information belongs to the Essentware business assets. Therefore when Essentware becomes owned by a third party as the result of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or bankruptcy, customer information is passed to this third party as well.

  4. _for protection of Essentware and others:_ if your Personal Information will be required by the government or legal institutions, we have the right to reveal it in order to comply with the law or protect our rights, property, employees, users, etc.

  5. _with your consent:_ you will be informed about other possible cases of sharing your Personal Information, and will have the right to prevent this.

## 7\. Security

We do everything possible to secure private information of our customers by implementing the newest data protection technologies. However, we cannot ensure the 100% security of your Personal Information. Various system failures or unauthorized access may jeopardize user information at any time. Should you navigate to some other websites from our website, please be aware that we are no longer responsible for privacy policies of other sites and services.

## 8\. Changes To This Policy

We will keep you up to date about any possible changes to our Privacy Policy. As soon as such changes occur, we will inform you either via email or via our website.

## 9.Questions or comments

We are open to any questions on this Privacy Policy. Please submit all your concerns to our email; you may also contact the Company in writing at Slovak Republic, 82104 Bratislava, Office Center “Aircraft”, Ivanska Cesta 30/B.
